{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "Answer: mouse", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["help", "lifted", "mouse", "so"]}, {"explanation": "went is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Is \"went\", Verb (past tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "tied is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Is \"tied\", Verb (past tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea _____________ the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["after", "in", "by", "of"]}, {"explanation": "After is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["of", "in", "by", "After"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: search", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["search", "to", "him", "of"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: wagon", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["the", "After", "a", "wagon"]}, {"explanation": "take is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to _____________ him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["let", "take", "help", "go"]}, {"explanation": "idea is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is \"idea\", Verb (non 3rd person singular present tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: that", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["so", "was", "and", "that"]}, {"explanation": "they is Personal pronoun", "question": "Is \"they\", Personal pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "The is Determiner", "question": "Is \"The\", Verb (3rd person singular present tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: him", "question": "In the following sentence identify Personal pronoun.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["him", "lifted", "of", "the"]}, {"explanation": "search is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in _____________ of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["idea", "mouse", "search", "tree"]}, {"explanation": "let is Verb (base form)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (base form) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and _____________ him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["let", "take", "go", "help"]}, {"explanation": "being is Verb (present participle)", "question": "Is \"being\", Verb (present participle) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "go is Verb (base form)", "question": "Is \"go\", Verb (base form) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: in", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["a", "him", "they", "in"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: tree", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["Sometime", "tree", "a", "few"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["to", "later", "him", "and"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: later", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adverb.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["later", "few", "a", "him"]}, {"explanation": "him is Personal pronoun", "question": "Is \"him\", Personal pronoun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After _____________ they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["in", "that", "by", "of"]}, {"explanation": "search is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is \"search\", Pural singular Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "let is Verb (base form)", "question": "Is \"let\", Verb (base form) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: lifted", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["go", "lifted", "tickled", "to"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: being", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (present participle).", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["being", "paw", "the", "the"]}, {"explanation": "of is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Is \"of\", Preposition or subordinating conjunction in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "hunters is Pural Noun", "question": "Is \"hunters\", Verb (past tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: that", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["they", "that", "to", "take"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him _____________ he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["of", "that", "by", "after"]}, {"explanation": "tree is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["lion", "paw", "idea", "tree"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: a", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["lion", "later", "and", "a"]}, {"explanation": "Sometime is Adverb", "question": "Select appropiate Adverb from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["later", "Sometime", "so", "sometime"]}, {"explanation": "by is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled _____________ the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["of", "that", "in", "by"]}, {"explanation": "captured is Verb (past participle)", "question": "Is \"captured\", Verb (past participle) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}], "success": 1}